airsquirrels.com 2016-10-28

# Squirrels Store - Apps to go nuts for.

Our privacy policy applies to information we collect when you use or access our website located at http://www.airsquirrels.com or purchase or use the AirParrot and Reflector native applications. We may change this privacy policy from time to time. We encourage you to review our privacy policy whenever you access our services to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy.

**COLLECTION OF INFORMATION**

Information You Provide to Us:  
We collect information you provide directly to us. For example, we collect information when you purchase items, subscribe, participate in any interactive features of our services, fill out a form, request customer support or otherwise communicate with us. The types of information we may collect include your name, email address, billing address and other contact or identifying information you choose to provide.

Information We Collect Automatically When You Use the Services:  
When you access or use our services, we automatically collect information about you, including:

  * Log Information: We log information about your use of our services, including the type of browser you use, access times, pages viewed, your IP address and the page you visited before navigating to our services.
  * Device Information: We collect information about the device you use to access our services, including the hardware model, and operating system and version. 

Information Collected by Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies:  
We use various technologies to collect information, and this may include sending cookies to your computer. Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive or in your device memory that helps us to improve our services and your experience, see which areas and features of our services are popular and count visits. We may also collect information using web beacons (also known as "tracking pixels"). Web beacons are electronic images that may be used in our services or emails and to track count visits or understand usage and campaign effectiveness. For more information about cookies, and how to disable them, please see "Your Information Choices" below.

**USE OF INFORMATION**

We use information about you for various purposes, including:

  * Providing, maintaining and improving our services, providing services you request, process transactions and to send you related information, including confirmations and invoices
  * Send you technical notices, updates, security alerts and support and administrative messages
  * Respond to your comments, questions and requests and provide customer service
  * Communicate with you about Squirrels-related news and information
  * Monitor and analyze trends, usage and activities in connection with our services; and
  * Personalize and improve our services.

By accessing and using our services, you consent to the processing and transfer of your information in and to the United States and other countries.

**SHARING OF INFORMATION**

We don't share your personal information with 3rd parties except those necessitated for the direct functionality of your purchase (such as our payment processors who handle the payment of your transactions).

We may share personal information about you as follows: If we believe disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request;

**THIRD PARTY ANALYTICS**

We may allow third parties to provide analytics services (such as Google Analytics). These third parties may use cookies, web beacons and other technologies to collect information about your use of the services and other websites, including your IP address, web browser, pages viewed, time spent on pages, links clicked and conversion information. This information may be used by Squirrels and third parties to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content and other websites and better understand your online activity. Our privacy policy does not apply to, and we are not responsible for, third party cookies, web beacons or other tracking technologies and we encourage you to check the privacy policies of these third parties to learn more about their privacy practices.

**SECURITY**

Squirrels takes reasonable measures to help protect personal information from loss, theft, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure and destruction.

**YOUR INFORMATION CHOICES**

Cookies  
Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can choose to set your browser to remove or reject browser cookies. Please note that if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of our services.

Promotional Communications  
You may opt out of receiving promotional emails from Squirrels by following the instructions in those emails. If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional communications, such as those about applications you have purchased.
